[Music]
Brother, this is what I need.  Order it right now.
So this is that glass kettle and look, there is a strainer attached to it.
Come let's check
how tea is made in this.  Ok.  So
first of all add some water,
some sugar and now add some
tea leaves in it.  Meaning, there will be
no need to filter the tea later using a strainer.  Now let's
place the cattle on top of it.  And here friend,
look at one thing, there is very little water here.  The
height of the sieve is a little
higher.  This means that one more cup of water will have to be added to it.
If you are making tea for at least three-four people
then tea can be made in this.
And look friend, now the sieve is immersed in it.
And look at the color of the tea, it has become a little
brown.  Now add milk to it.
And look friend, a lot of smoke is
coming out of it.  But yes, whatever you see, this glass is
borosilicate glass.  Meaning
no tension at all.  You can put it on the gas.
So now let's add this milk into it.
And a second has fallen out a little bit.
Now let's see what kind of tea is made in it.
And look friend, your tea is ready.   Let's
take it out in a cup and pour the
tea.  And look at this, friend.
Look at this brother.
So yes, according to me, this
cattle is absolutely worth the money.